# Design Generalist



Loves <u>UI/UX</u>, <u>CSS</u>, <u>UX writing</u>, and <u>using data</u>. Specializing in <u>Design Systems</u> & <u>Conversion Optimization through research</u>. 15 Year career grounded in telling stories and persuading through design. Thrives making complex visions clear.

Seeking: remote, permanent, positive impact, large projects, mentoring opportunities.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **iMARKET SOLUTIONS**

Designer 9/2015 - PRESENT

Designed hundreds of lead-generating websites for contractors. Additional 50% of the role was improving processes: helping establish a 3-day design turnaround, creating & maintaining pattern library, incorporating design critiques, and creating internal best practices. 2 years as Design Team CRO Representative: AB testing, heatmaps, research.

**Developer** 9/2014 - 9/2015

Developed 22 custom, responsive websites using MODx, HTML, CSS, and JS.

#### **FREELANCER**

Owner, etc. 1/2013 - 2015

Ran a small design consulting studio in Gift-Economy. Work included: Project Strategy, WordPress Web Development, Branding, UI/UX.

#### ADLIFE MARKETING

Web Consultant

Designer for startup. Built small sites for local businesses. Also: Sales, Account Management, and Development.

#### FIDELITY INVESTMENTS

Designer `2013

Designed and developed ads following their design system using Flash, InDesign, and HTML/CSS.

## BRADY PEOPLE ID

### Graphic Designer

2006 - 2013

Designed logos to print for an ID company - think lanyards and badge holders. Also managed 2 remote Designers and was trained in LEAN.

# **EDUCATION**

## SUNY ONEONTA

Graphic Design B.A.

## UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN

EdX MicroMasters, UX Research and Design